Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is Netflix and chilled. Let me show
you how to make it. We are starting off
with a peanut butter base. Haven't done
this one on the channel in so long, but
we're going to need 400 g of fat-free
fairife milk, 16 g of a powdered peanut
butter, 8 g of a regular peanut butter,
some sweetener, some salt, and some
zantham gum. And then we're just going
to blend that up and throw it in the
freezer for at least 16 hours. Once it's
completely frozen through, you can take
it out and run under hot water for about
a minute and then throw it in your
creamy on the light ice cream set. It'll
probably come out a little bit powdery
like mine did. So, you can just take it
out and scrape down the sides with a
butter knife and throw it back in the
creamy on the respin setting. Now, while
that is respinning, we can grab our
mixins. I'm using a Prime Bites protein
brownie because they're delicious. They
taste just as good as a regular brownie
and they pack 19 grams of protein. I'm
using the PB&J flavor. I know this
flavor usually has chocolate brownies,
but I had these PB&J ones. And then just
add a beautiful peanut butter flavor.
Then you can just finish it off with
some pretzels and you're good to